<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chef Habitat Builder on-prem documentation</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Chef Habitat Builder on-prem documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Artifactory</title>
      <link>http://example.org/artifactory/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/artifactory/</guid>
      <description>Using Artifactory as the object store (Alpha) If you are interested in using an existing instance of Artifactory as your object store instead of Minio, we are providing this capability as an early preview/alpha for testing.
To set this up, you will need to have the following:
 Know the URL to the Artifactory instance Know (or generate) an API key to authenticate to the instance Create a repo for the Habitat artifacts  Once you have the above, modify the your bldr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>builder.env</title>
      <link>http://example.org/builder-example/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/builder-example/</guid>
      <description>#!/bin/bash  # The endpoint and port for your Postgresql instance # Change only if needed export POSTGRES_HOST=localhost export POSTGRES_PORT=5432 # The endpoint, key and secret for your Minio instance (see README) # Change these before the first install if needed export MINIO_ENDPOINT=http://localhost:9000 export MINIO_BUCKET=habitat-builder-artifact-store.local export MINIO_ACCESS_KEY=depot export MINIO_SECRET_KEY=password # If you&amp;#39;d like to use Arifactory instead of Minio, uncomment # and set the following variables appropriately. # IMPORTANT: See the README for more info # export ARTIFACTORY_ENABLED=true # export ARTIFACTORY_API_URL=http://localhost:8081 # export ARTIFACTORY_API_KEY=foo # export ARTIFACTORY_REPO=habitat-builder-artifact-store # Modify these as needed for the on-premise OAuth2 provider.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chef Habitat Builder on-prem</title>
      <link>http://example.org/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Chef Habitat Builder on-prem Umbrella Project: Chef Habitat
Project State: Active
Issues Response SLA: 5 business days
Pull Request Response SLA: 5 business days
IMPORTANT NOTICE Please see the Migrating Package Artifacts to Minio if your existing Chef Habitat Builder on-prem was installed prior to June 15th 2018. The package artifacts are now stored in a Minio instance, and running a migration script will be required in order to properly transition over to newer versions of Chef Habitat Builder on-prem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minio Migrations</title>
      <link>http://example.org/minio-migration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/minio-migration/</guid>
      <description>Migrating Package Artifacts to Minio This section is for installations of On-Premise Depot that were done prior to June 15, 2018. If you re-install or upgrade to a newer version of the On-Premise Depot, you will be required to also migrate your package artifacts to a local instance of Minio (the new object store we are using). Please follow the steps below.
Pre-requisites  Install the following Habitat packages:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Postgres Migration</title>
      <link>http://example.org/postgres/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/postgres/</guid>
      <description>Postgres Migration Merging Database Shards This section is for installations of On-Premise Depot that were done prior to August 17th 2018. If you re-install or upgrade to a newer version of the On-Premise Depot, you will be required to also merge your database shards into the public Postgres database schema. Please follow the steps below.
Shard Migration Pre-requisites  The password to your Postgres database. By default, this is located at /hab/svc/builder-datastore/config/pwfile A fresh backup of the two databases present in the On-Premise Depot, builder_sessionsrv and builder_originsrv.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>